Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Presidents Files, 1923-1994; 416.34 Linear feet (417 boxes)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Religion, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 980, Folder 2-14)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Residences, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 980, Folder 15-17)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Residences, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 981, Folder 1-4)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Science, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 981, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Security (Personal), 1960-1989 (Offsite-box 981, Folder 6-8)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Sketches, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 981, Folder 9-18)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Sketches, 1944-1965 (Offsite-box 982, Folder 1-14)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Social, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 982, Folder 15-18)
    The folders containing materials from January through June 1961 include copies of the Kennedy Family Tree.
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Space, 1958-1969 (Offsite-box 983, Folder 1-7)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Speeches, 1963-1993 (Offsite-box 983, Folder 8-15)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Speeches, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 1063, Folder 1-18)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Speeches, 1953-1961 (Offsite-box 1064, Folder 1-12)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Speeches and Diction, 1960-1968, 1974-1987 (Offsite-box 1064, Folder 13-16)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Staff, 1959-1969, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1064, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: State of the Union, 1961-1965, 1983 (Offsite-box 1064, Folder 18-20)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: State of the Union, 1961 (Offsite-box 1065, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Taxes, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 1065, Folder 2-17)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Trade, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 1066, Folder 1-12)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Transport, 1960-1979, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 1066, Folder 13-14)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Travel, 1963-1985, 1993 (Offsite-box 1066, Folder 15-16)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Travel, 1947-1952, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 1067, Folder 1-10)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: United Nations, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 1067, Folder 11-14)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Visitors, 1960-1968, 1979-1984, 1991 (Offsite-box 1067, Folder 15-17)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Welfare, 1954-1970 (Offsite-box 1067, Folder 18-19)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald: Youth, 1959-1969 (Offsite-box 1068, Folder 1-2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 1068, Folder 3-17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: General, 1937-1964 (Offsite-box 1069, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Administration, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1069, Folder 4-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Advertising, 1964-1970, 1976 (Offsite-box 1080, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Advisers and Assistants, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1080, Folder 2-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Appointments, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1080, Folder 15-18)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Appointments, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 1081, Folder 1-13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Archives, 1964-1993 (Offsite-box 1081, Folder 14-16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Awards and Honors, 1958-1985 (Offsite-box 1082, Folder 1-6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Awards and Honors, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 1093, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Books, etc. (About), 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 1082, Folder 7-18)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Books, etc. (About), 1969 (Offsite-box 1093, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Books, etc. (By), 1954-1980 (Offsite-box 1083, Folder 1-2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Cabinet, 1965-1988 (Offsite-box 1083, Folder 3-16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Cabinet, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 1084, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Cartoons, 1959-1976, 1989 (Offsite-box 1084, Folder 4-8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Characteristics, 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 1084, Folder 9-17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Characteristics, 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 1085, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Clothing, 1949, 1960-1981, undated (Offsite-box 1085, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Clubs and Societies, 1955-1970 (Offsite-box 1085, Folder 5-7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Congress, 1966-1987, 1993 (Offsite-box 1085, Folder 8-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Congress, 1949-1965 (Offsite-box 1086, Folder 1-11)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Correspondence, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1086, Folder 12-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Correspondence, 1955-1967 (Offsite-box 1087, Folder 1-7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Domestic, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1087, Folder 8-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Domestic, 1941-1965 (Offsite-box 1088, Folder 1-13)
    Folder 13, which contains materials from 1941 through 1956, includes a signed letter from 1956. During this period, President Johnson was a United States Senator from Texas as well as the leader of the Democratic Party. The letter discusses a questionnaire that the Senator had completed for Fortune. The questionnaire that asked questions about current events and United States policies, is also included in the folder.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Family, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 1088, Folder 14-16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Family, 1945-1947, 1954-1966 (Offsite-box 1089, Folder 1-4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Finances, 1941, 1953-1982, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1089, Folder 5-8)
    Folder 8, which contains materials from 1941 through 1964, includes two copies of a report on the assets and liabilities of the Johnson Family.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Foreign, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 1089, Folder 9-16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Foreign, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 1090, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Foreign, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 1091, Folder 1-13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Foreign, 1948-1964 (Offsite-box 1092, Folder 1-12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Friends, 1967-1988, undated (Offsite-box 1092, Folder 13-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Friends, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 1093, Folder 5-6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Gifts, 1961-1981, 1987 (Offsite-box 1093, Folder 7-9)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Health (Personal), 1965-1991 (Offsite-box 1093, Folder 10-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Health (Personal), 1937, 1951-1968, undated (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 1-2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Inauguration, 1960-1977, 1988, undated (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 3-5)
    Folder 4, which contains materials from 1965, includes an inauguration program.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Jokes and Skits, 1956-1986 (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 6-9)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Kennedy, Robert F, 1966-1979 (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 10-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Monuments and Sculptures, 1964-1979, 1985 (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Legal Action Against, 1975 (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Names and Titles, 1960-1978, 1988, undated (Offsite-box 1094, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Non-Political Career, 1984 (Offsite-box 1095, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Paintings and Pictures (Of), 1956-1986, 1993 (Offsite-box 1095, Folder 2-4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Pets, 1959-1974, 1985 (Offsite-box 1095, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 1095, Folder 6-17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1096, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1097, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 1098, Folder 1-13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1964 (Offsite-box 1099, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 1120, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Politics, 1937-1963 (Offsite-box 1121, Folder 1-11)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Polls, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 1121, Folder 12-14)
    Folder 13, which contains materials from 1968, includes a copy of a report titled, "A Preliminary Report on a Study of Public Reaction to President Johnson's Decision Not to Seek Reelection."
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Polls, 1956-1967 (Offsite-box 1122, Folder 1-7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Possessions, 1960-1973, 1980 (Offsite-box 1122, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Powers and Duties, 1959-1982 (Offsite-box 1122, Folder 9-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Powers and Duties, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 1123, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Press Conferences, 1956-1979, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1123, Folder 2-9)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Press Relations, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 2681, Folder 15-16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Press Relations, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 1123, Folder 10-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Press Relations, 1957-1966 (Offsite-box 1124, Folder 1-8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Quotes, 1971-1977 (Offsite-box 2681, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Quotes, 1958-1971 (Offsite-box 1124, Folder 9-12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation, 1961-1970, 1982, 1993 (Offsite-box 1124, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: A-Z, 1960-1970, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 1124, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Architecture, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Art, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Baseball, 1955, 1964-1968, 1980, undated (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Broadcasts, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Dancing, 1962-1967, 1978, 1988 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Football, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Golf, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: History, 1955, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Horses, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Hunting, 1954-1969 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Music, 1958-1970, 1981 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Photography, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Reading, 1961-1972, 1979 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Sailing and Swimming, 1963-1967, 1975 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Theater and Cinema, 1961-1975, 1985 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Recreation: Walking, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Religion, 1959-1983, 1991 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 17-22)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Residences, 1967-1983 (Offsite-box 1125, Folder 23-24)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Residences, 1959-1966 (Offsite-box 1126, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Security, 1956-1975, 1981-1985, 1993 (Offsite-box 1126, Folder 4-8)
    Folder 4, which contains materials from 1969 to 1993, includes a list of secret service code names for presidential families from President Johnson through President Clinton.
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Sketches, 1969-1983, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1126, Folder 9-13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Sketches, 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 1127, Folder 1-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Sketches, 1939-1965 (Offsite-box 1128, Folder 1-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Social, 1968-1981 (Offsite-box 1128, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Social, 1957-1967 (Offsite-box 1129, Folder 1-6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Speeches, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1129, Folder 7-13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Speeches, 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 1130, Folder 1-12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Speeches, 1942, 1948-1957 (Offsite-box 1131, Folder 1-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Speeches and Diction, 1961-1981 (Offsite-box 1131, Folder 4-6)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Staff, 1956-1970, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1131, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: State of the Union, 1964-1972, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 1131, Folder 8-14)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Transport, 1957-1978 (Offsite-box 1132, Folder 1-2)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Travel, 1961-1982, 1993 (Offsite-box 1132, Folder 3-12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Visitors, 1968-1979, 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 1132, Folder 13-15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines: Visitors, 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 1133, Folder 1-5)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: General, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 1133, Folder 6-13)
    Folder 7, which contains materials from 1989 through 1991, includes a list of political opponents. This list is in order of priority and has an evaluation of each person.
  - Nixon, Richard M.: General, 1972-1975, 1993 (Offsite-box 1134, Folder 1-18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: General, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1135, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: General, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 1136, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: General, 1948-1966 (Offsite-box 1137, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1137, Folder 18-19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 1138, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1139, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration, 1951-1969 (Offsite-box 1140, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Advertising, 1968-1976, 1990 (Offsite-box 1140, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Advisers and Assistants, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 1140, Folder 17-19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Advisers and Assistants, 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 1141, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Advisers and Assistants, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 1142, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Advisers and Assistants, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 1143, Folder 1-5)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Appointments, 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 1143, Folder 6-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Appointments, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 1144, Folder 1-8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Archives, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1144, Folder 9-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Archives, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1145, Folder 1-14)
    Folder 13 contains a copy of the Review of a Report Submitted to the U.S. District Court of Columbia Entitled "The Tape of June 20, 1972".
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Archives, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1146, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Archives, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1147, Folder 1-4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Awards and Honors, 1948, 1954-1992 (Offsite-box 1147, Folder 5-9)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Books, etc. (About), 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 1147, Folder 10-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Books, etc. (About), 1956-1970 (Offsite-box 1148, Folder 1-3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Books, etc. (By), 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1148, Folder 4-9)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Cabinet, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1148, Folder 10-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Cabinet, 1968-1973 (Offsite-box 1149, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Cartoons, 1954-1987 (Offsite-box 1150, Folder 1-4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Characteristics, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 1150, Folder 5-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Characteristics, 1952-1974 (Offsite-box 1151, Folder 1-14)
    Folder 12, which contains materials from January through June 1969, includes four astrological births charts that were created for President Nixon.
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Clothing, 1954, 1969-1990 (Offsite-box 1151, Folder 15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Clothing, 1954-1961, 1968 (Offsite-box 1152, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Clubs and Societies, 1954-1983, 1990 (Offsite-box 1152, Folder 2-4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 1152, Folder 5-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1153, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 1154, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1970 (Offsite-box 1155, Folder 1-12)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1156, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Congress, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 1157, Folder 1-4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Correspondence, 1952-1991 (Offsite-box 1157, Folder 5-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Domestic, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 1157, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Domestic, 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 1158, Folder 1-18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Domestic, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 1159, Folder 1-22)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Domestic, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 1180, Folder 1-27)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Domestic, 1948-1968 (Offsite-box 1181, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Family, 1953-1993 (Offsite-box 1182, Folder 1-11)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Finances, 1974-1984, 1990 (Offsite-box 1182, Folder 12-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Finances, 1952-1974 (Offsite-box 1183, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1183, Folder 16-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 1184, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1185, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 1186, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 1187, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1188, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 1189, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1959-1968 (Offsite-box 1190, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Foreign, 1951-1959 (Offsite-box 1191, Folder 1-3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Friends, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 1191, Folder 4-10)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Gifts, 1953-1963, 1969-1983, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 1191, Folder 11-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Health (Personal), 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1191, Folder 14-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Health (Personal), 1948-1974 (Offsite-box 1192, Folder 1-8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Health (Personal) [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R27)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Impeachment, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 1192, Folder 9-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Impeachment, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1193, Folder 1-3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Inauguration, 1953-1961, 1968-1996 (Offsite-box 1193, Folder 4-9)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Jokes and Skits, 1952, 1960-1992 (Offsite-box 1193, Folder 10-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Legal Actions Against, 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 1193, Folder 16-18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Legal Actions Against, 1974 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 1-9)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Monuments and Sculpture, 1959, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 10)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Names and Titles, 1968-1980, 1987 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 11)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Non-Political Career, 1961-1968, 1985-1992, undated (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 12)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Paintings and Pictures (of), 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 13-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Pets, 1952-1974, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Pictures (Of), 1958-1974 (Offsite-box 1194, Folder 16-18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1195, Folder 1-11)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1974 (Offsite-box 1196, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1197, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 1198, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 1199, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1235, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1236, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1968 (Offsite-box 1237, Folder 1-20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1968 (Offsite-box 1238, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1239, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 1240, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 1241, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1960 (Offsite-box 1242, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1952-1959 (Offsite-box 1243, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Politics, 1946-1952, undated (Offsite-box 1244, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Polls, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1244, Folder 2-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Polls, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 1245, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Possessions, 1967-1982, 1992 (Offsite-box 1245, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Powers and Duties, 1970-1982, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 1245, Folder 3-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Powers and Duties, 1952-1970, 1982 (Offsite-box 1246, Folder 1-8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Conferences, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1246, Folder 9-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Conferences, 1956-1972 (Offsite-box 1247, Folder 1-8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Relations, 1974-1991 (Offsite-box 1247, Folder 9-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Relations, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 1248, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Relations, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 1249, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Press Relations, 1952-1959 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Quotes, 1958-1991 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 2-8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation, 1958-1959, 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 9)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: A-Z, 1962, 1968-1990 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 10)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Art, 1968-1982 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 11)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Baseball, 1947, 1953-1989 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 12)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Bowling, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Dancing, 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Fishing, 1952-1955, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Football, 1953-1959, 1969-1988 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Golf, 1953-1977, 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: History, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Horses, 1963, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Music, 1953, 1962-1988 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Radio and Television, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 21)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Reading, 1953, 1965-1984 (Offsite-box 1250, Folder 22)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Sailing and Swimming, 1968-1974 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Skiing, 1960, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Sports, 1955-1960, 1968-1976, 1985, 1992 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Tennis, 1955-1957, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Recreation: Theatre and Cinema, 1960-1974, 1985 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 5)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Religion, 1953-1983 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 6-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Residences, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 1251, Folder 14-20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Residences, 1952-1973 (Offsite-box 1252, Folder 1-6)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Resignation, 1973-1991 (Offsite-box 1252, Folder 7-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Security (Personal), 1954-1992 (Offsite-box 1253, Folder 1-6)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1974-1994 (Offsite-box 1253, Folder 7-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 1254, Folder 1-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 1262, Folder 1-19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 1263, Folder 1-16)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1948-1968 (Offsite-box 1264, Folder 1-12)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches [RESTRICTED], 1956-1959 (Offsite-box R22)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Sketches, 1946-1950, undated (Offsite-box 1265, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Social, 1957-1992 (Offsite-box 1265, Folder 2-11)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1265, Folder 12-17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1266, Folder 1-13)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 1267, Folder 1-15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 1268, Folder 1-14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches and Diction, 1973-1977, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1268, Folder 15)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Speeches and Diction, 1956-1972 (Offsite-box 1269, Folder 1-2)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Staff, 1958-1981, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1269, Folder 3-4)